hamidashita kaze wo atsumete mitai na
I want to try and gather the unrestrained winds
nami no saki tsutatte kanata e kaketeku
I'll run toward the horizon alongside the wave crests
kakugo wa kimatteru
I've made my decision
michi wa tookutemo
even if there's a long way to go on that road
egaita mirai e tsudzuiteru
I'll continue towards the future I've planned
toki ga bokura wo sekashite kodou ga supiido agetetta
time rushes us, the heartbeat speeds up
yume no naka de mezametemo onaji hikari wo sagashita
when I woke in the middle of a dream, I kept searching for that same light
kagayaku hoshizora no shita kazoekirenai seiza to kage
under the shining star-lit sky, with countless constellations and shadows
sono saki ni kimi wa nani wo nani wo mitsumete iru darou
there was something beyond that, what were you gazing at?
nani wo mitsumete iru darou
what were you gazing at?
Sea Battle
The Released Power
So, you're a monster, too!
You're one to be acting
like you are above me!
Take this!
What?!
Crap!
This is bad!
Naruto!
I'm counting on you...
Naruto! Hang in there.
Naruto!
I'm okay...
Isaribi... Thank you.
Oh, no!
I'll take the rest of your Chakra!
Mind Destruction Jutsu!
Impossible!
Made it in time...
What?!
I see... It was you, huh?!
The nerve of you to mess with me!
Stop it, get away!
Don't turn your back to the enemy...!
You forgot the ironclad rule
of the fight...
You lose!
You saved me...
That brat hit me with all his strength...
And that Yoroi is no good either.
I caught a huge fish!
You mean you're going
to escape alone?
We completed accommodating
all the injured soldiers.
Good work!
What's left is...
Naruto and others, right?
Of your numerous crimes...
When we return to the village
justice will be served,
and it won't be quick,
so prepare yourself.
It's not over yet...
You! I haven't hit you enough yet!
That's too bad.
What?!
What... What's going on?
The Sea Monster doesn't die.
It is immortal, that one!
For the Sea Monster,
this limitless seawater is its life...
In the end, it will be your loss!
Shut up!
Summoning Jutsu!
All right! I'm counting on you, Chief.
Go clobber that flabby guy!
Hey, Chief! We don't have time
for you to be so leisurely!
That monster...
Whack him in one go...
That's hot! Hot, hot!
You got no business getting
so motivated all by yourself!
It itches, itches
and I'm getting a rash all over my body!
Wait, wait.
Don't come over here, Naruto!
Damn him...
I'm going to rip you apart
when the mission is over!
Remember that!
Naruto! How are you going
to settle this?!
How can you say that,
Chief Toad is the strongest frog!
Please don't let something like
the salt water bother you and fight.
You can't even control
the summoned animal you called up!
What was that?!
If you don't send him home quickly
the Sea Monster will gulp him down
and he'll whither like a slug!
A slug, he says?!
Hey, Naruto! I'm going to
kick your butt later...
Right now, I'll help you.
Huh? For real?!
Don't mess with amphibians...
I'll show you my terror!
Yeah! Now you're talking.
Hang on!
What the...?
You rat... Let go of me, huh!
What is this? He got you, Chief Toad!
You be quiet!
Upsy!
This isn't accomplishing anything...
What's up with
that flabby bastard, really?
In short, this is some kind of monster
consisting of water gathered around
its spiritual body at the core.
Crap!
I don't really know what that means,
but I guess I can't do anything
about that thing.
Even though we pierce the monster
with a dagger all we want,
the monster will suck up ocean water
and come back to life...
Then what should we do,
Chief Toad?!
The only thing we can do here is
to somehow damage
the spiritual body at the "core."
Damage...? How?
The opponent is a clump of water...
Add heat and he'll evaporate!
The thoughts of fools mean nothing...
The only thing you can do is to
surrender to me, I who control the ocean!
Damn. You're annoying.
Let's go, Naruto!
What? Go? Where are you going?!
Airhead! I'll spew oil!
Light a fire with
a Fire Style Jutsu!
What?! I can't do
Here we go!
What? Fire, fire, fire!
How's that?!
What?!
He did it...!
Well done!
Naruto...
Im... Impossible!
We did it, Chief Toad!
How's that!
Me and Chief Toad are
the strongest combination, after all!
Naruto! You're in a festive mood
all by yourself,
though I'm wondering if
you've forgotten about something?
Huh? Forgotten what?
You called me to a place like this...
Look, now I've got all of
these goose bumps!
You've always had all those warts...
Shut up! I'll have you
settle this properly!
What?! Wha...?
Wait Chief Toad! Wait!
No use talking!
It itches. I can't take it!
Something like this
doesn't soothe my feelings but,
my sons have caused you inconvenience,
so I forgive you this time.
See you!
I'm sorry, Chief Toad... Help me...
Now that we also got rid of
the Sea Monster, Amachi...
You'll be taken to
the Village Hidden in the Leaves
as the principle offender
of the attacks on ships collecting funds.
Shame! We had gotten kicked
around because of you!
What are you doing?!
Isaribi, kill these guys!
I won't!
Have you forgotten?
I am the only person
who can turn you back into a human!
If I continue doing this,
I'll be a monster all the way
to my heart!
That's right, Isaribi!
You're neither a human being
nor fully integrated like me.
The best you can do is to live
the rest of your life as a monster
for your whole life!
Well, from the very start,
I hadn't thought of a way
to turn you back into a human!
Like I told you...
I was intending to dissect you!
No way...
You!
How rotten are you?!
Stop it.
Once we've returned to the village,
he'll be punished harshly.
Well... It's about time you told us.
Where... did Orochimaru go?
You think I know something
like that?!
You were tossed aside
by Orochimaru.
It serves you right to follow
after him forever.
You and I are different!
I'll be in charge of the research center
and someday will become an entity
that'd bring Orochimaru to shame.
Really...
Just for yourself. Not fair!
And now, mission completed.
Let's return to the island!
Not fair. I'm also slug
a good one before that.
Stop it!
That's the Jiro Island
Amachi was talking about...
Here is the source of my nightmare...
This place is where the fragments
of my missing memories are left.
Orochimaru-sama...
What in the world did you...?
She's alive...!
She's a lucky girl...
After we tested ten,
only one survived...
I guess this experiment yielded
a little something before I take my leave.
Leave...?
Because it looks like
there's no reason to be here anymore...
But, the research is still...
That facility, do with it
whatever you want.
I have no need for it anymore...
— Why...? How could you do this?
— I always respected you, yet you...
You're lacking many things.
Motivation to desire the "power"...
Tenacity...
Hatred...
Everything!
But, let's see...
I suppose just the fact
that you survived
might mean you have some value...
Say? Do you want to come with me...?
I see...
I'll find a better gifted child then...
It connected...
So bright...
I wasn't cast aside...
I, on my own...
by my own will... chose it!
Hey, hey, where did Sensei go?
When I woke up this morning
she wasn't here...
Leaving behind only a note like this!
Will be right back! Anko
Seriously...
She sure is a fidgety person!
What did you say?
Who do you think you are?
Whaddya mean?!
What, you object?!
Really... Can I come with you?
Don't worry!
There's a very scary,
but awesome Medical Ninja
in Village Hidden in the Leaves!
Yes, because Tsunade-sama
is a medical specialist.
That's right, Tsunade-sama is amazing!
Surely she'll do something for you!
Relax and let us take care of it.
Thank you.
Hey, all of you!
What are you doing?!
The boat will leave!
When did you...!
What were you doing?!
We've been waiting for you
this whole time, Sensei.
Sorry, sorry...
Wait! We're getting on!
Okay! We're going home
to the Leaf Village!
No doubt, you are hyper
from the start to the finish...
Do you know what being tired is?
Any problem?
I'm praising you! I appreciate it!
Huh? Really?
You're embarrassing me.
kaze ga fuite aa
the wind blows
itai kienai omoi
the pain, the memories won't disappear
nani wo motte ikou ka
what should be brought along?
atsumete hitotsu
assemble them into a piece
nido to nai nido to nai
there is no second chance, never
suteru nante baka mitai
how foolish it is to throw away
mujaki ni natte aa
acting so innocently
imeeji
the images
kitto sore wa owaranai
it probably will not end
ai no mune kogase
burn that love-filled heart
sen no yume watare
sail across a thousand dreams
juuoumujin kakete
running freely
te ni tsukamu sekai
to take hold of the world in hand
kumo ga chigirete
the clouds scatter
hi ga mata ochite
the sun sets yet again
hitori no pareedo ga ugokidasu
the solo parade begins to move
bouken kichijitsu shinpaku joushou
adventure, lucky day, geart beat, rising
meian souguu seimei souai
decisive, encounter, life, mutual love
Guarding a high-profile individual.
Sure has a nice ring to it!
Yeah! A mission has finally come
that suits my ability!
Just you wait,
you great heir to a fortune!
Now that I've taken this on,
I'll go through fire or water or...!
Hey, what's this?!
Isn't this just a D-rank mission
with babysitting?
Next time: "Impossible. Celeb Ninja Technique - Money Style Jutsu!"